boardingarea.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy - BoardingArea

At BoardingArea we are just as concerned about privacy as you are, maybe even more so.

It is our goal to protect your privacy when you visit or participate in any of our blogs and to make your online experience safe and enjoyable. Because we collect certain types of information about you when you visit our blogs, we have written this Privacy Policy to share our practices and use of that information.

### Types of Information We Collect:

**– Anonymous Information**  
We collect anonymous information from our visitors that cannot be associated with a specific individual. For example, we know how many people visit BoardingArea, but we don’t know their names or any other personal information about them. We collect this type of anonymous data in order to track overall Web site traffic and the specific pages that people visit most often. This anonymous tracking information is used to build a better service and enhance the content in our most popular blogs. Some of this anonymous tracking information is shared with third parties such as advertisers, but again, it remains anonymous.

**– Comment Information**  
Individual blogs store the comments you leave on their blog when responding to a bloggers post if we are hosting that blog. This information is yours, and is never used by BoardingArea for purposes other than what you intended. Just remember which blog you left a comment on, BoardingArea itself does not have any comment areas.

**– Personal Information   (application in becoming a blogger on BoardingArea only)**  
We collect personal information if you voluntarily join the family of BoardingArea bloggers. Registration is required to access some of the features of this service. The only personal information collected upon signing up for a hosted blog is a working email address.

**– The Way We Use Information (application to become a blogger only)**  
We use your email address to send a confirmation email when you sign up for a hosted blog or when you choose to participate in the private bloggers only forum and to allow you to reset your password if you lose or forget your old one. We will also send you a notice to let you know if your blog has been accepted or declined. And finally, our administrators might send you an email if circumstances warrant it. No other use is now or ever will be made of this email address. We will not send you any other email unless you contact us first and specifically request information, technical help, or administrative assistance. We do not sell this address, or link it to any other personal information.

**– Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure any information (which is very, very limited) we collect online.

**– Cookies**  
Occasionally BoardingArea or its advertisers and/or sponsors may need to place a “cookie” on your computer or in our emails/communications. A cookie can serve many purposes such as a history of your previous visits to BoardingArea or your screen name, email and URL if you decided to leave a comment on a blog post. Cookies do not usually create any problems for you or your computer and are generally silent bystanders. They are primarily used to create a unique user experience for you on BoardingArea and in an age of personalization—to deliver more relevant advertising to you only via **nonpersonal information**  that this cookie and your other cookies may offer. **You are free to delete this cookie at any time and you can elect to refuse cookies and/or delete cookies at any time in the future.** If you choose to do so, any information that was collected on past visits to BoardingArea will not be stored. **The choice is always yours, and we in no way discourage you from taking your privacy into your own hands and in fact encourage it.**

To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt out, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices.](https://app.grooveapp.com/url/qhc4aywsry3t1mhw1wfwh/aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYm91dGFkcy5pbmZvL2Nob2ljZXM%3D)

### Links to Other Sites

BoardingArea contains content links to blogs—that’s the ‘network’. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any of these blogs as they retain and have their own complete ownership of the content you read there. BoardingArea owns no content.

**– Surveys or Contests**  
From time to time we sponsor surveys and contests. If you participate, the sponsor typically will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you will have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Contest information typically includes information such as name and mailing address. If we are directly involved, we only use this information internally to determine eligibility, notify contest winners, and to measure the success of our efforts. Absolutely nothing else.

**– Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
While we don’t anticipate any changes in our privacy policy, there is always a possibility of change. If there is any substantial change to our policy, we will post those changes on pages we deem appropriate so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

This policy was last modified on February 1, 2019.

**– Contacting BoardingArea**  
If you have additional questions, please contact us by email at [privacy@boardingarea.com](mailto:privacy@boardingarea.com), or write to us at:  
**BoardingArea**  
415 E. Pikes Peak Avenue #101  
Colorado Springs. CO 80903  
(USA)

Randy Petersen  
President, Frequent Flyer Network
